<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MotionLayout Playground</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="scene_one_info">OnSwipe transition attached to rectangle. You can drag it up and down or release, then object will position nicely at start or end constraint depends on release position</string>
    <string name="scene_one_title">Scene 1</string>
    <string name="scene_two_title">Scene 2</string>
    <string name="scene_two_info">OnClick action attached to rectangle. This action start transition to start or transition to end.</string>
    <string name="scene_three_title">Scene 3</string>
    <string name="scene_three_info">During swipe we are changing custom attribute, which is background color, from blue to red</string>
    <string name="scene_four_title">Scene 4</string>
    <string name="scene_four_info">In this scene, we added keyFrameSet with one keyPosition that locates the box on the left side of screen exactly at 50th frame of animation(out of 100)</string>
    <string name="scene_five_title">Scene 5</string>
    <string name="scene_five_info">This scene have two additional KeyAttributes, which set scale. The first is responsible to scale up the view to 150% in 25th frame and second is responsible to scale down to 75% in frame 75th.</string>
    <string name="scene_six_info">This scene combines keyPositions and keyAttributes. One responsible to position the view in X/Y and second responsible for changing it scales to look more natural</string>
    <string name="scene_six_title">Scene 6 - leaf</string>
    <string name="sceneSevenTitle">Scene 7(text)</string>
    <string name="sceneSevenInfo">This scene contains two views, box and text. After box end the transition, the text changes. CustomAttribute with `customStringValue` is used to change text</string>
    <string name="sceneEightTitle">Scene 8(swipe)</string>
    <string name="sceneEightInfo">This scene shows swipe effect. We have two transitions here - like/dislike and three slightly different constraintSet - rest, like and dislike</string>
    <string name="sceneNineTitle">Scene 9</string>
    <string name="sceneNineInfo">This scene is similar to scene eight, but upon swipe left/right the view fly off the screen. This is possibly using another constraintSet and auto transitions.</string>
    <string name="scene10Title">Scene 10(square reveal)</string>
    <string name="scene10Info">This scene have very simple animation, but what is important is that at the end of animation it opens second fragment. Check the Scene10Fragment.class to see how to implement TransitionListener</string>
    <string name="scene11info">Added ItemTouchHelper.Callback to RV to check how the horizontal swipe works. I have problems to implement rotation</string>
    <string name="scene11title">Scene 11(ItemTouchHelper)</string>
</resources>
